const week2Data = [
  {
    question: "Based on functionality, MQTT is a _______ protocol.",
    options: ["Transport", "Data", "Semantic", "None of these"],
    answer: "Data",
  },
  {
    question: "MQTT is designed for -",
    options: [
      "Remote connections",
      "Limited bandwidth",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "Neither (a) nor (b)",
    ],
    answer: "Both (a) and (b)",
  },
  {
    question:
      "MQTT protocol follows _____________ paradigm for exchanging messages.",
    options: [
      "Client-Server",
      "Publish-Subscribe",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "Publish-Subscribe",
  },
  {
    question:
      "State True or False. Statement: “In MQTT, the Subscribers are Lightweight Sensors.”",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is MQTT component?",
    options: ["Middleman", "Mules", "Both (a) and (b)", "None of these"],
    answer: "None of these",
  },
  {
    question: "State True or False. A topic in MQTT can only be numbers.",
    options: ["False", "True"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "State True or False. There are only two methods specified by the MQTT protocol.",
    options: ["False", "True"],
    answer: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Publish/Subscribe architecture in MQTT is __________ driven.",
    options: ["Event", "Pulse", "Sound", "None of these"],
    answer: "Event",
  },
  {
    question:
      "State True or False. The topic is the routing information for the broker.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "CoAP is _____________ and ____________.",
    options: [
      "Based on HTTP",
      "Is designed for M2M applications",
      "None of these",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
    ],
    answer: "Both (a) and (b)",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In CoAP, client-server interaction is asynchronous over a datagram transport protocol such as ____________.",
    options: ["UDP", "TCP", "IP", "XMP"],
    answer: "UDP",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the full form of AMQP?",
    options: [
      "Advanced Message Querying Protocol",
      "Advanced Message Quality Protocol",
      "Advanced Message Queuing Protocol",
      "None of these",
    ],
    answer: "Advanced Message Queuing Protocol",
  },
  {
    question: "AMQP has _______ number of frame types.",
    options: ["6", "3", "5", "9"],
    answer: "9",
  },
  {
    question: "State True or False. Statement: “The OSI model has 7 layers.”",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The “Destination Address” in the IPv4 packet represents which of the following?",
    options: [
      "The source node address of the packet",
      "The intermediate hop in the network",
      "Both (a) and (b)",
      "Neither (a) nor (b)",
    ],
    answer: "Neither (a) nor (b)",
  },
];
